{
    "id": "859f20952d334353b9731f9bce8d456a",
    "title": "Conjunctions And Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Keep a candle ready ……………………… the lights go out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "in case"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "787ad1931c694a8dbd1fbf00b9593e95"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. the rain has stopped, we can resume the journey.",
            "description": "Now that is similar to as or because. ",
            "answers": [
                "Now",
                "Now that",
                "So"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cdb60999ecbf43afb12c044bd11126ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. a bridge has been built over the river, you can reach there by car.",
            "description": "Now that is similar to as or since or because.",
            "answers": [
                "That",
                "If",
                "Now that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a07921762ef240078f2ee78766113a83"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. he was in Pune, he visited a number of factories there.",
            "description": "While can indicate time. It is similar to when.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "While",
                "Whereas"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fd886d1506db496288bc15c7e4aa5a61"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her clothes caught fire …………………………… she was cooking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "as",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "81b00bc3a8b14eaba934119deb1cd9ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. he was having a bath, the telephone rang.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "While",
                "Since"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "af46fb7e37484b2988c220bf01700a50"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………….. he receives immediate treatment, his condition may worsen.",
            "description": "Unless is similar to if...not...",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "Until"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fbeb593428124bb6a52425c2b14e3c58"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… being poor, they are very happy.",
            "description": "In spite of is a preposition. Only a preposition can be used before an ing form. ",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d22e5d059fe54ae5aaba1451cb40599d"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… being famous, he failed to win the election.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c3640386478e43528109abe5b5f66542"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. you go, you will find mosquitoes.",
            "description": "Wherever means it doesn't matter where.",
            "answers": [
                "Where",
                "Which",
                "Wherever"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4aeeed75e3484636ac83d13470dce3df"
        },
        {
            "question": "He brings nice gifts …………………………….. he visits us.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whenever",
                "wherever",
                "however"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9766db515133411ba2c62cc164b83dc8"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. he worked, he made several good friends.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Wherever",
                "Whenever",
                "Ever"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "052dae4fa9384bf3a91b2eb87ba0b5bc"
        }
    ]
}